​

1-800-645-3122

[0 Items](https://www.littletoncoin.com/shop)Your Current Order

​

###### About Littleton

* * *

* About the Company

* * *

* Our Policies

* * *

* Contact Us

* * *

* Learn About Collecting

Littleton Coin Company's Privacy Policy
=======================================

_Last updated March 2024_

 Thank you for placing your trust in Littleton Coin Company! We've been serving collectors since 1945. Please note that our ordering systems do not currently service residents of the United Kingdom or European Union.

At Littleton Coin Company, we believe understanding our customers' needs and expectations for products, services and information is an important part of building an enjoyable, interesting and satisfying long-term relationship. Therefore, we've created this page so you can have easy access to information about our privacy practices and how we use the information we may collect. Littleton Coin Company's privacy policy ("Policy") describes the information we collect, how we use it, who we share it with and how we secure it.

By using our website, you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information as described in this Policy, and you also agree to our Terms of Use, which are expressly incorporated into this Policy. Please read this Policy and our Terms of Use carefully.

Information We Collect
----------------------

We receive information from you when you visit LittletonCoin.com in order to personalize your experience. This includes when you:

* Visit our website
* Place an order on our website
* Place an order from our catalogs
* Make a purchase in our retail store
* Request a catalog
* Pay for Club or Approval selections
* Create an online account
* Subscribe to our email newsletter
* Sign up to receive text alerts and offers
* Return or exchange an item
* Receive a gift order
* Participate in a promotional event
* Enter a sweepstakes or contest
* Join our mailing list
* Take a survey
* Share your stories, photos or videos
* Contact our friendly customer service department via phone, mail, email, chat or social media
* Apply for a job

The information you choose to share may include:

* Name
* Mailing address
* Phone number (including cell phone)
* Email address
* Order information (including credit card information)
* Customer number
* Birthdate
* Photos or videos
* Military Affiliation (armed forces branch, years of service, status)
* Level of collecting experience and who you are buying for
* Collecting interests shared through survey or correspondence via phone, mail, email, chat or social media

Occasionally we ask for information about collecting experience, numismatic interests, the way you buy coins and your age range. Although sharing it is totally optional, we use this information to learn about collectors, your coin interests and your experience so we can provide you with better information and offers.

We also receive the content of any mail or email messages you send to Littleton Coin Company, including information on your resume, if you send it to us. If you call Customer Service or chat with us using our Chat functionality on the website, please be advised that your conversations are recorded.

Cookies and Pixel Tags
----------------------

A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your web browser directly on your computer. Some cookies are necessary for our website to function properly and enable you to place an item in your cart and to checkout. Other cookies allow us to enhance your shopping experience. Please note that if you set your browser to reject all cookies, our website may not function properly.

Cookies may collect information such as:

* Details of your visits to our website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources you access and use on the website
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type

Cookies enable you to place an order on our website. They also allow us to collect information to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience, so the information you receive is more relevant to you, and to measure the success of our marketing efforts. For example, we use cookies to:

* Remember what items are in your shopping cart
* Recognize you when you return to our website
* Enable faster checkout if you have created an account on LittletonCoin.com
* Deliver personalized marketing from Littleton Coin Company
* Study how our customers navigate through our website and which products they request in website searches

We also contract with third-party service provider Google Analytics. Google Analytics uses cookies to help analyze how you use the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google in aggregate form. Google may use this aggregated information in order to evaluate use of the website, compile reports on the website's activity and other services relating to website activity and usage. You can learn more about Google Analytics and how to opt out here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Most internet browsers allow you to block or delete cookies and other similar technologies from your browser. If you do not agree to the use of these cookies or similar technologies, please disable or delete them by following the instructions for your browser or use automated disabling tools where available. Please note that if you reject cookies, you may still use our products and services but your ability to use some features of our products and services may be limited. If you set your browser to refuse cookies, please call us at [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122) to place your order.

We also use pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to tell us what parts of our website you have visited or to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send you emails in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us.

We may also contract with third-party advertising companies to collect data and to serve ads on our behalf across the internet. To do this, they will collect information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements. To learn more about your choices regarding this type of data collection or to opt out of interest-based advertising, please visit the following sites:

How We Use the Information We Collect
-------------------------------------

Littleton Coin Company has a tradition, since 1945, of providing quality coins, paper money, related products and services that consistently meet or exceed our customers' needs and expectations. To do this, we collect information that enables us to:

* Process and track your order (name, address, telephone number, email address)
* Provide order status updates and order tracking
* Contact you about the status of an order (name, address, telephone number, email address)
* Maintain a record of your purchase and provide you access to your order history
* Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you (name, address, telephone number, email address)
* Send you the Littleton Coin email newsletter (name, email address)
* Identify your product and service preferences (name, customer number, order history and account details, collecting preferences)
* Personalize our communications to you (name, telephone number, email address)
* Provide information concerning products you have purchased (name, telephone number, email address, order history)
* Improve our merchandise selection and customer service

We may use the information we collect when you visit our website to better fulfill your order, or to better serve you with the products and services we offer. We may periodically contact you by email, traditional mail or telephone with information about your order or our products and services.

_How we use email:_ Littleton Coin Company sends emails regarding the status of your order, including one email to confirm each order you place online and another email to alert you when the order has shipped. We may use email to contact you with questions regarding your order. We use email to answer your online questions to us or requests for information. We send email newsletters containing promotions of products and services, news, trivia and information about upcoming events. Occasionally, we may contact you via email to ask for permission to reprint what you have written, as a testimonial, for use on our website and social media or in our advertisements, emails and printed materials.

Abandoned Cart Information
--------------------------

Littleton Coin Company uses cookies to collect information around abandoned shopping carts. A cart is considered abandoned within one hour of inactivity/lack of purchase. Once the cart is considered abandoned, an SMS message will be sent as a reminder to those customers who have opted into our SMS marketing program; additionally, an email will be sent as a reminder to customers who have provided an email address.

Sharing Information With Others
-------------------------------

Littleton Coin Company does not sell your personal information. We only share your personal information with companies we contract with in order to conduct normal business.

We contract with other companies to provide certain business services. When those third parties need personal information, we require that your privacy remain protected. These services include:

* Credit card authorization
* Payment processing
* Shipping
* Email distribution
* Text distribution
* Ratings and reviews, market research and surveys
* Advertising and promotions (including targeted advertising)

We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services, and we work closely with them to ensure your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from sharing or using this information for any reason other than to complete the business purpose we have contracted them to provide.

Littleton Coin Company does not rent or sell your name, address, phone number, email address or other information we collect to other companies for marketing purposes. If any business claims to have obtained this information from Littleton Coin Company, please call us right away toll free at [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122) and provide us with the company name and contact information, if possible.

* * *

| Categories of Sources from which the Information was Collected | Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which Information is Collected | Categories of Third Parties to whom this type of Personal Information is Disclosed for a Business Purpose | Categories of Third Parties to whom this type of Personal Information is Sold/Shared |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| * * *<br><br>Identifiers, such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet Protocol address or account name, telephone number and gift card information |     |     |     |
| * Directly from you when you place an order, or provide it to us in connection with a service you request<br>* Automatically, when you visit our websites<br>* From third-party sources, such as data brokers, or third-party social media platforms | * To complete your order or service request, or to communicate with you<br>* To provide our websites and their functionality to you<br>* To analyze and understand our customers' preferences and use of our sites and services<br>* To inform our marketing efforts<br>* To better tailor our product and service offerings and to market them to you | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Characteristics such as marital status, veteran or military status and sex (including gender) |     |     |     |
| * Directly from you<br>* From third parties, such as data brokers or social media platforms | * To better personalize your experience and our marketing efforts | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We do not share this data with third-party marketing services. |
| * * *<br><br>Commercial information, including records of products or services purchased |     |     |     |
| * Directly from you, when you make a purchase from us | * To complete your order<br>* To comply with legal obligations<br>* To analyze our business, inform inventory and product decisions and inform marketing efforts | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history and information regarding a consumer's interaction with an internet website application or advertisement |     |     |     |
| * Automatically, when you visit our websites | * To provide our websites and their functionality to you<br>* To analyze the use of our sites and performance of our business and marketing efforts, and to improve the functioning of our sites and the effectiveness of our marketing | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Inferences drawn from any of the above information to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities and aptitudes |     |     |     |
| * We may draw these inferences ourselves or acquire them from third-party data resellers. | * To help us better personalize your experience, our websites and our marketing efforts | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Sensitive Personal Information |     |     |     |
| * When you place an order, we will collect your payment information | * To process your order | * Service providers, such as payment processors | * We do not use or disclose Sensitive Personal Information for any reasons other than the permissible business purposes set out in Cal. Civ. Code Sec. 1798.140(e) (2), (4), (5) and (8), and as authorized by regulations adopted by the California Privacy Protection Agency. |

How We Correct or Update Your Personal Information
--------------------------------------------------

We maintain information about our customers so that we can better serve you. You may review or update the personal information we have collected at any time by contacting us through email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.littletoncoin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), calling us toll free at [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122) or logging into our secure website and updating your Personal Profile.

Unsubscribe
-----------

If you'd rather not receive mailings, email, text or other communication from Littleton Coin Company, please contact us at:

Littleton Coin Company, Inc.  
1309 Mt. Eustis Road  
Littleton NH 03561-3735  
Toll-free phone: [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122) (from anywhere in the U.S.)  
[\[email protected\]](https://www.littletoncoin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

When contacting us, please be sure to give us your exact name and address or the mailing label from your catalog so we can identify you correctly. Because our mailings are planned in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective.

If you no longer want to receive our email newsletter, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions provided in each issue of the email newsletter or by sending us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.littletoncoin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with "unsubscribe" typed in the subject field.

Your Privacy Choices
--------------------

_If you are a resident of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah or Virginia, you have the following additional rights._

* Request to Know: You have the right to know whether we are processing your personal information and request that we disclose a report of your personal information, including the categories and specific pieces of personal information we have about you, the categories of sources from which the personal information has been obtained, the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling or sharing personal information, and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose personal information (as well as which categories of information were disclosed). Any such information should be provided in a format easily understandable to the average consumer, and to the extent technically feasible, in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. For additional information and to request your report, you may [click this link to our "Your Privacy Choices"](https://www.littletoncoin.com/shop/Your-Privacy-Choices) page, or you may send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.littletoncoin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or call us at [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122).
* Request to Delete: You have the right to request that we delete your personal information. Once we receive and verify your request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies. For additional information and to request deletion of your personal information, you may [click this link to our "Your Privacy Choices"](https://www.littletoncoin.com/shop/Your-Privacy-Choices) page, or you may send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.littletoncoin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or call us at [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122).
* Request to Correct: You have the right to request that we correct, rectify and/or update any of your personal information that is incorrect, incomplete or out of date. If you have created an online account, you may log on and edit your personal information at any time. If you are unable to edit your personal information through your online account, you may send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.littletoncoin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or call us at [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122).
* Request to Opt Out: You have the right to direct us not to sell or share your data for purposes of cross-context behavioral marketing, and the right to opt out of the processing of personal information for purposes of targeted advertising. You may [click this link to our "Your Privacy Choices"](https://www.littletoncoin.com/shop/Your-Privacy-Choices) page to exercise your right to opt out, or you may send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.littletoncoin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or call us at [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122).
    
    If exercised, the decision to opt out will be valid for 12 months, at which time we may request that you authorize the sharing of personal information for marketing purposes again.
    
* Statement re: the Use or Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information: Littleton Coin Company does not use or disclose sensitive personal information or sensitive data, as such is defined in The Connecticut Act Concerning Personal Data Privacy and Online Monitoring, The Utah Consumer Privacy Act, Colorado Privacy Act, Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act and the California Privacy Rights Act.

How to Exercise Your Privacy Rights
-----------------------------------

When you contact us to exercise your rights to know, delete or correct your personal information, we will first verify your identity by asking you to confirm a few pieces of information we have in our records, such as your email address, phone number or address. With a request to correct, we may require information from you to demonstrate that our information is incorrect. This information shall only be used and/or maintained by the business for the purpose of correcting your personal information and to comply with any record-keeping obligations we may have under the law.

You may use an authorized agent to exercise your opt-out rights described above. For avoidance of doubt, parents may make a verifiable request on behalf of their minor child to exercise any consumer rights described in this policy.

You may make a verifiable consumer request up to two times within a 12-month period, without charge. Unfortunately, we cannot respond to your request to delete or correct, or provide you with personal information, if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm that the personal information relates to you. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us.

We try to respond to a verifiable consumer request within 45 days of its receipt, and an opt-out request will be processed within 15 business days. If we require more time to respond to a verifiable consumer request, we will inform you of the reason and extension time period (up to 90 days). If you have an account with us, we will deliver our response to the email associated with that account. If you do not have an account with us, we will deliver our response by mail or electronically, at your option. The response we provide will also explain any reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable.

You have a right to appeal any denial of a consumer right. If your request is denied in whole or in part, you have the right to appeal your decision within 30 days. We will review and respond to your request within 45 days, and if your appeal is denied, we will provide you with an explanation of our reasons and a description of any further rights you may have at that time.

Right to Equal Service: We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights as a consumer under any applicable laws. Unless permitted by law, we will not:

* Deny you goods or services.
* Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
* Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
* Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

We may offer you certain financial incentives permitted by law that can result in different prices, rates or quality levels. Any legally permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal information's value and contain written terms that describe the program's material aspects. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt-in consent, which you may revoke at any time.

For California Residents Only
-----------------------------

Notice at Collection

The Personal Information we collect about you will depend upon how you use our website and interact with us. The below chart describes the categories of Personal Information, as defined under California law, that we may collect about you when you visit our website or interact with us, the Business Purpose for which the data is collected and how the information may be shared or sold. This chart also describes the manner in which Personal Information was collected and used within the past 12 months.

* * *

| Categories of Sources from which the Information was Collected | Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which Information is Collected | Categories of Third Parties to whom this type of Personal Information is Disclosed for a Business Purpose | Categories of Third Parties to whom this type of Personal Information is Sold/Shared |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| * * *<br><br>Identifiers, such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet Protocol address or account name (Cal. Civ. Code. §1798.140(v)(1) |     |     |     |
| * Directly from you when you place an order, or provide it to us in connection with a service you request<br>* Automatically, when you visit our websites<br>* From third-party sources, such as data brokers, or third-party social media platforms | * To complete your order or service request, or to communicate with you<br>* To provide our websites and their functionality to you<br>* To analyze and understand our customers' preferences and use of our sites and services<br>* To inform our marketing efforts | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Categories of Personal Information as defined in Cal. Civ. Code §1798.80, including, but not limited to, name, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, driver's license or state identification card number, education, occupation or field and gift card information |     |     |     |
| * Directly from you<br>* From third parties, such as data brokers or social media platforms | * To complete your order or service request, or to communicate with you<br>* To better tailor our product and service offerings and to market them to you | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Characteristics of protected classifications under California Law, including race, ethnicity or national origin, marital status, veteran or military status and sex (including gender) |     |     |     |
| * Directly from you<br>* From third parties, such as data brokers or social media platforms | * To better personalize your experience and our marketing efforts | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We do not share this data with third-party marketing services. |
| * * *<br><br>Commercial information, including records of products or services purchased |     |     |     |
| * Directly from you, when you make a purchase from us | * To complete your order<br>* To comply with legal obligations<br>* To analyze our business, inform inventory and product decisions and inform marketing efforts | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history and information regarding a consumer's interaction with an internet website application or advertisement |     |     |     |
| * Automatically, when you visit our websites | * To provide our websites and their functionality to you<br>* To analyze the use of our sites and performance of our business and marketing efforts, and to improve the functioning of our sites and the effectiveness of our marketing | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Inferences drawn from any of the above information to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities and aptitudes |     |     |     |
| * We may draw these inferences ourselves or acquire them from third-party data resellers. | * To help us better personalize your experience, our websites and our marketing efforts | * Service providers who facilitate the provision of a requested service, or support our business purposes described in the previous column | * We may share information with third-party marketing services as described in the "Sharing Information with Others" section above. |
| * * *<br><br>Sensitive Personal Information |     |     |     |
| * When you place an order, we will collect your payment information. | * To process your order | * Service providers, such as payment processors | * We do not use or disclose Sensitive Personal Information for any reasons other than the permissible business purposes set out in Cal. Civ. Code Sec. 1798.140(e) (2), (4), (5) and (8), and as authorized by regulations adopted by the California Privacy Protection Agency. |

Links to Other Websites
-----------------------

On our website, we provide links to other sites we think you will enjoy. These other sites operate independently of Littleton Coin Company and have established their own privacy and security policies. We encourage you to review the privacy and security policies of any sites you visit. Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Policy or our website's Terms of Use. We are not responsible for the data collection, use practices, policies or cookie use of the third-party sites that you access from our website.

Security
--------

Littleton Coin Company takes reasonable and appropriate measures to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the personal information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security. If you have any questions about our security, you can contact us at [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122).

Privacy of Children Using Our Website
-------------------------------------

Littleton Coin Company's website is not intended for use by children under the age of 18. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information on the website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on this website. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

Policy Changes
--------------

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time. Any updates we may make to our Policy will be posted on this page, and we may also provide a notice of any material changes on our website for a reasonable period of time. Whenever we make updates, we will revise the "last revised" date at the top of this Policy. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Policy.

How to Contact Us
-----------------

If you have any questions or feedback regarding this privacy policy, we welcome you to contact us at:

Littleton Coin Company, Inc.  
1309 Mt. Eustis Road  
Littleton NH 03561-3735  
Toll-free phone: [1-800-645-3122](tel:1-800-645-3122) (from anywhere in the U.S.)  
[\[email protected\]](https://www.littletoncoin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Join Our Email List

Sign Up

Call Toll Free

M–F 7:30 a.m. – 9:00 p.m. ET

M–F 7:30 a.m. – 9:00 p.m. ET

In the area?

Gift Shop Hours: M–F 9:00 a.m. – 4:00 p.m. ET.  
Free tours held M–F at 1:30 p.m. ET.

Shopping Services

Customer Support

Buy with Confidence

© 1998-2024 Littleton Coin Company, Inc. All rights reserved.  
1309 Mt. Eustis Road, Littleton, NH 03561
